Hi everyone.
If you saw the last record, welcome back. I'm Yue.
Maki here.
What's today's plan?
Today we are going to Amakusa.
Amakusa, Amakusa... Oh, I remember!
A friend from school said she was often going there to fish.
Are we going there to fish too?
Too bad! No fishing today. I've never fished anyway.
You never did? Well, I didn't either.
Why the taunt then...
Today we are mostly riding on the coast line.
And... I kind of want to take pictures somewhere.
I'll wait or rather I'll walk around.
Nono, I'll make it quick!
It's fine. I want to walk around again.
Sorry. I'll try to be fast.
It's ok. I'm sure it'd take me 3 or 4 hours just to get there.
And you don't have to feel sorry about having fun.
You're coming to have fun right?
Thank you.
I'm having fun too so don't worry too much.
Wasn't Amakusa on the sea side?
It is on the sea side.
I'm only seeing mountains for a few.
Indeed.
Hope you have a good explanation.
Ahh, roads on Amakusa are often jammed so I go through a detour.
You cannot see the sea here and when we'll cross the island.
Is that so? Well, I'm enjoying the view.
Oh! It's a bit far but is that the sea?
You have good eyes!
That land is Nagasaki so would that make the Ariake Sea?
It's so pretty from here.
Right? There is many viewing spot here.
Like you said, no cars around. Just your motorcycle, sky, sea and the two of us.
Maybe some animal is looking from between the trees.
And maybe it'll jump across the road.
Ahaha... Stop. You are making me scared.
Oh?! We're almost at the sea.
Really? I'm excited! I wonder if it's as blue as everyone says.
Not sure about the colour but you can almost see it.
Ohhh!
Woaahh!
You never saw the sea?
I've seen some inland sea but never a proper one. Didn't expect it to be this big.
This is the Amakusa Sea. Since it's next to the East China sea, it seems endless.
Yeah, it's so huge!
I wonder if we can swim here?
I don't think so... there is a lot of current here.
Is that so... it's a shame...
So many good roads to ride on.
Too bad you cannot see places like this with public transport only...
I might have said it earlier, but it really helps a lot because
it'd take me 3 or 4 hours just to get here.
That's hard...
At least I can get here.
The sea is really close...
It is. This cliff sure makes the view better.
I feel like I can almost touch it.
Hey! Don't lean too much!
Ow sorry! I'll be careful.
It's okay.
?
What is?
Feels like... It is a dead end... but not.
Phew, it is just a detour.
Glad it's not a dead end?
Yeah. Since this is the only road, we would have to make a huge detour.
The road is becoming narrower.
Bye-bye centre line.
You're pretty calm. Aren't you scared?
I'm uneasy thinking about oncoming cars, but that's why you lower the speed.
Is that so... I'm scared, but I love this kind of roads.
It feels like it could lead anywhere.
I get you. Feeling like it leads to some far far place.
Sure is a good road.
Wait... a bus... here?!
It's pretty narrow but nothing to be surprised at all.
It has to go through small tunnels like the one in front.
Wait... I cannot see incoming cars...
Just be ready to stop and it's going to be ok.
I cannot see... Hope noone is coming...
Oh! We pretty high up.
We have almost arrived.
Okie
See you later!
Have a good time!
Seizure warning for 10 seconds.
Hope this setting is ok.
Hop!
... I see...
How about this!
...
Hop!
Yop!
Yah!
Ha!
*sigh*
Mhhh
Not good either...
How about this!
Better.
Why is he leaping about...
Nailed it!
The view there seems good too.
Wait, did Maki?!
It seems she isn't back yet...
Just have to move the motorcycle over there.
Yup. Nice view. Perfect to wait for Maki.
I'm back!
Welcome back. How was it?
Was fun. Not many viewpoints but the sea was cracking.
That's good to hear! Ready to go?
Let's go!
I found a beach down there do you think we can swim?
Got curious too and looked up and it is the Shiratsuru beach so I think you can swim.
But, you've never seen the sea right?
Never. I've been to pools and water theme parks but I've heard it's nothing like that?
I don't like swimming per say, but I find it relaxing.
I went to a water theme park once with friends and keep good memories.
Is that so? I'm not fond of the sea... Actually not fond of swimming in the sea.
A pool is plenty to swim... But I'm interested in sailing and diving...
Is that so...
Ah, true. Going alone isn't fun. How about swimming with Aoi?
There's a plane from Osaka to Amakusa.
Wouldn't that make us need to ride the motorcycle with three persons?
It's going to be fine if you make yourself small.
Disclaimer: do not ride with three persons on the bike.
But you'll have to wait alone while we're swimming.
Don't worry about it.
There seems to be a campsite nearby, so I'll enjoy myself there.
You sure you don't want to come to the beach? You can see us in our swimsuits!
It's ok. I'm happier if you two go along.
I want to see!
Ok, I need to find a swimsuit first tho...
I'm pretty sure there are 5 to 6 months until we can swim in the sea.
You don't want to come and pick one with me?
It's ok, it's ok. There's a lot of time to choose one.
Cutie
You said you wanted to try out something at the campsite but you like camping?
I have only camped once.
I slept a few times in a tent when trekking up the mountains but,
I've been told that's not camping.
I'm surprised you even trekked in the first place.
Trekking is fun since you can see a lot of pretty places from high up!
High up...
Ah, I remember something. Can we go to Amakusa's airport?
Okay. It's a small shortcut but I hope the road is empty.
Thanks I wanted to see that blue plane.
You like planes?
Not a huge fan but I find the small ones cute.
Hope you can see it.
Haven't checked the timetable. I'm pretty sure we won't be able to.
We'll see.
Hey, we are almost at the airport.
Here to the left.
Migi and Hidari... I always get confused.
Used to say left then right so feel odd to say right, left...
Ahh, I feel you. Left is the side you have your fork in... Who's left is it?
Or when driving in the city all day long you hear turn left, turn right, turn left, turn right,
left, left, right, left... That's tiring...
Yeah, I feel you...
You always use the GPS? Why not turning it off?
I'm starting to know the place so when not in a hurry I leave it off.
You don't get lost often?
I'm always left behind even if the GPS is right.
Huh!?
I'm sorry...
Ain't a fan of word puns. Sorry for overreacting...
No, my bad. I'll be careful from now on.
Can you hear it?
Yue, quick! We might have a glimpse of it!
Go first. I'll find a place to stop the bike.
kay, I'm good with that!
You lucky there is a space to see the runway.
I'm pretty excited to see it takeoff.
Oh look it's going to fly!
It's gone.
Indeed.
Let's go back but want to go somewhere first.
I'll wait outside.
Come, I want you to take a pic.
It's unusual for you to take a pic. But I don't think there is anything in this direction...
It's fine. Here we are. Take a shot around here.
Here?
Nahhh...
Say cheese!
There is nothing to take here but is that ok?
Perfect!
Hope you'll get some comments from this.
You sure know a lot...
I'm sure there will be comments but don't want to leave that in the record...
Hey, you should keep it. It's memories of stuff that happened.
Ok ok, I'll leave it in.
Just according to keikaku.
Note: Keikaku means plan.
Said something?
Nope nothing!
Is that so? Time to go back to Kumamoto.
Okay!
Ooyano flower road... wonder if it's good...
It's pretty empty here.
The sun is in our back, so the shadows are long.
Indeed but I cannot look behind.
Sure want to stop if there's a nice spot.
But it seems like there is no such spot.
Amakusa... Wait a sec.
Amakusa-Style Remix of Church.
Are there churches nearby? I thought Christians were many in Nagasaki.
They were mainly in Nagasaki but some Christian were in Amakusa too.
If only I could remember earlier.
It's okay. We can go next time since it's close.
Yeah, if I can remember next time.
Hope it wasn't too boring to be on the backseat all day long.
Nono, you took me to the airport.
And I could have walk when you were taking yourself.
You saw that?
Hehe, I chose the wrong path and came back.
I did not notice it at all...
You were busy hoping around.
It's ok to drive all day long.
I'm a bit jealous only you can drive tho...
But at the same time I don't know much...
Thinking of getting a bike lately... Go to close places by myself and far with you.
A bike? Like a moped?
Nono, a normal road bike.
Oh, a road bike. I used to ride one back in the days too.
Really? That's great. We can go together.
Next time.
I guess I will need to train again.
But I don't have much pocket money atm. Will take a few to save up.
Just take your time.
Phew...
I feel like there was more internal thought this time.
Sure. You said it'd be better to leave it in.
Was that too much?
Uzai... not sure of the meaning but I don't think it's annoying.
That's roughly it. But that's embarrassing so don't want to use it too much.
Yeah, after all I can hear it all.
Ah true that means Aoi...
Aoi!
Yes.
Sorry!
No need to call the police!
Wait. I'm underground but can you hear me?
Huh? Hello? Hellooo?
It cut.
... hello? hello...
And you wonder why she's nagging.
I'll listen to the lecture later.
Thanks for all the views and comments.
That's my line...
Well, it's becoming a template so might as well.
Template... It's true there isn't much change...
You should maybe think for another way?
You think? ... But I feel like thinking makes it sound fake.
You're not wrong.
Thank you for trying to make this a fun record.
You don't have to say that while recording. You better cut that.
Why? It's memories of events that happened!
Don't spout nonsense and let's react to some comments!
Indeed. Thanks for the comments.
How's it?
I'm not sure for others but since I already was I'll take it as a compliment.
oh kay...
That is a nice way to put it.
It does fit pretty well. I didn't think about this.
Thanks you for your interpretation.
How's it?
What's yan?
It's about Yankees.
I'm not an American...
Wha?
Ahh, this time it's for delinquents.
Are you a delinquent?
Who knows?
To speak it's not that hard, but it is indeed tricky to write.
Now need to compile the next record. But I think it'll take longer this time.
Please look forward to the next record.
Well see you on the next record until then take care.
See you!