Today is hanami!!! I'm excited!
You were this excited?
You bet, it's the first time I'm properly seeing one.
We can see some but sadly on the other side of the river.
Yeah, but it's already pretty from far away.
Ohhhh!
Happy to see some on our side too.
It's already pretty pretty.
Clouds are slowly going away, but I hope it'll get sunny on arrival.
Leave it to me! I'm pretty lucky with the weather.
That good to hear. Make sure it stays sunny!
Yes sir!
First time seeing cherries?
I've seen some near my school, but they are sparse.
Today we are going to one of the top 100 cherry blossom spot.
I cannot wait.
But the view is already amazing.
Oh? We're almost there.
Already?
Oh wow! Trees are so close!
Indeed, this place is great.
How is it?
It's great.
That's good to hear.
Great, it's open. Can we make a small stop?
Okay!
Hmmm, hard to take a picture.
Maybe change this?
Like this?
Sorry, the other way around.
Ready to go?
Sad to leave but let's go.
The road is still going so there still a lot to see.
Yay!
Thanks for bringing me here.
You are welcome.
This road is really pretty...
Look for as long as you want.
Sorry, I will probably be silent for a few.
It's all good.
I've never seen such beautiful cherry blossom back home...
I didn't know there were cherries overseas.
There isn't many but a few places have cherries. But many times it's just half a dozen of them.
That's great! You can have a small taste of Japan thanks to those.
Back home cherries are often in a small area inside a park.
You don't hear much Japanese but you see some cosplays.
There is cosplay oversea too?
There is! Not as high quality as Comiket but there is.
That was a blast!
Bloody hell...
Ay yo!
It's so pretty here too!
Right?
But this place looks very man made.
Well yeah.
Completely different in style but both have their good!
Been a long time since I came to Minamata.
You already came here?
Yeah. It's on the southern edge, and you can use the national road 3 to get here.
I never heard of this place until lately...
Hey. Can we make a stop at the museum? Always wanted to come here since I saw that movie.
Sure. It's close and I also wanted to visit that place.
Thank you.
There were more things than I expected...
Yeah. It was larger than I expected.
There was a lot of explanation, and it was very interesting.
I liked how the museum was split in three parts.
One for mercury, one for art and one for the events...
Yeah. It felt like each parts had a very different atmosphere.
You were walking a bit fast no?
Well, I don't like reading a lot...
I prefer to see the items rather than reading a wall of text...
Ah, I get you. But there were some interesting descriptions.
Yeh, that's why I was reading at first when they explain the effects of mercury.
Then when it was about the actions from the people, I was barely reading...
I think seeing the items and making a story in your head is more interesting.
Sometimes I want to be sure and read the description.
You have a point. This way you can remember things longer.
People back then didn't know a lot about those substances.
Mercury, lead, radioactive paint...
I cannot believe there is still places that uses such dangerous products.
Many don't really have the choice tho...
Now able to pass on one more thing.
Remember them.
Remember they once lived.
There is still plenty of time, want to go somewhere else?
Can we go to the mountain side please?
Okay.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot for today.
Likewise. Completely forgot about hanami.
A friend of mine said you don't go for the view, but for the drinks...
Ahh...
Yah, there is people like this...
I see seeking every occasion to drink is an international thing.
Haha, you're right.
It's already this late...
Oh gosh... I don't want to study for exams.
That's sounds hard...
Wait, was it ok to go watch the flowers today?
It'sallright!
I'm already behind schedule.
What did all right ment again...
That sounds hard... Good luck!
Thanks! I'll do my best!
Finally done... Now just have to...
Going to explain why it took you so long to post?
Well... There is a deep reason. Deeper than the Mariana Trench.
Go on.
It tried to create a script for this video but...
since I couldn't find it funny, I decided to try other was to create my video.
So weekly post from now on?
Weekly is a bit much... But I'll try to post more stuff even if I have to change topic.
Well, you have to make the subtitles two times after all...
I first need to have a dialog to make the subtitles.
You write scripts you don't use in the end.
Ahh, I cannot hear anything!
Thanks for all the view and comments for the dating past video.
Comments...
Kind of want to read and not read them...
Is there something wrong?
Well, you made me take a specific picture...
C'mon it's going to be all right.
You sure?
Thanks for the cheering.
You always smirk to those.
I don't smirk... or do I?
Yay!
It's true you see a lot individually, but pretty rare to see mixed up.
400X good!
I guess people are used to hear English nowdays...
Well Maki speaking English is good too.
Don't say silly things and got to the next comment.
Okay okay.
Yeah, why? Have my guess but...
Ah, this is a homage to Kureo, a young man appearing in videos made by Okara called SR400 Touring Diary.
So this was the Kureo jump... But why?
Well, I'm a bit chubby so wanted to do some exercice.
And to train shooting moving object.
You could take birds or trains...
...
Didn't think about that...
I just make myself small and hide in a pocket.
There is no space to sit behind...
It's just some hidden setting.
Who's that?
See! Told you people would comment on this.
But this is just a 3 digit number.
I don't know what everyone is on about.
Isthatso...
I'm sorry if it made you uncomfortable.
I didn't try to annoy you. It's just a friendly taunt.
Well, it's a must do if you see this number.
You seems tiered today, are you alright?
Yah I'm okay... Just having a lot of exams lately...
Exam, That's a word i didn't hear in a long time... Good luck!
I'll!